Guide to the Frauke Heard-Bey and David Heard collection AD.MC.064
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Business and economics, general, 1969-2017
  - UAE Quarterly Forecast Report. Q1, 2002 (Business Monitor International, Ltd.) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - The UAE Business Forecast Report. Q4, 2006 (Business Monitor International, Ltd.) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - UAE Offsets Group (UOG) News, Volume X, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - UAE Offsets Group (UOG) News, Volume XIV, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - UAE Share Directory, (Abu Dhabi: National Bank of Abu Dhabi), 1996 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - The United Arab Emirates Medical and Health Services Directory (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - WorldCare Gulf Directory 1998: Private Medical Care in the United Arab Emirates (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Culture and general, 1972-2016
  - Abdullah, Muhammad Morsy. The United Arab Emirates: a modern history. (London: Hurtwood Press). Spiral bound copy of galley proof, 1994 (Box Oversize 1)
  - Abu Dhabi Culture and Heritage: Administrative council meeting (agenda, slides, notes), November 2, 2008 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Abu Dhabi Culture and Heritage: Organization Design Recommendations, draft presentation presented to board. (print out of slide show), 2010. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Abu Dhabi 2005 International Hunting and Equestrian Exhibition Show Guide (Emirates Falconer's Club) (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Abu Dhabi 2007 International Hunting and Equestrian Exhibition [program] (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Al Burda Festival. Shaping the Future of Islamic Art and Culture. Abu Dhabi [festival program], 14 November 2018 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Al-Ma'arid al-mushtarak al-thalith lathar majlis al-ta'āwun liduwal al-Khalīj al-ʻArabīyah = Third Joint Archaeological Exhibition of the Council of Cooperation of Gulf Arab States (Al Ain: Dept. of Antiquities and Tourism)., November 1, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - American Arab Affairs. [photocopies of two issues: No. 13 and No. 16], Summer 1985 and Spring 1986 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Arabian American Oil Company. The Eastern Provinces of Al Hasa [photocopy of 1950 research paper] (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Arabian Horse Stud Book, Vol. 2. 1993 (Abu Dhabi: Emirates Arabian Horse Society (Volume 12)
    SF293.S8.A735 Vol. 2 1993
  - Art Hub, Abu Dhabi. Live, Create, Exhibit (Two booklets, describing activities and programs), undated circa 2013-2014 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Asil Club. Asil Araber: Arabiens edle Pferde. (Hildesheim: Olms Press, 1980) (Volume 13)
    SF293.A8A84 1980
  - Asil Cup International. Ergebnisse / Results. Hessische Landgestüt, Dillenburg, 5. bis 7. September 1986 [pamphlet] (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Books-Made in the UAE: New Emirati Children's Books (Goethe Institut / UAE Board on Books for Young People), undated, circa 2015 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Center for Documentation and Research. Presidential Court: Prospectus and CD-ROM, describing activities, holdings of archives, exhibitions. English and Arabic, undated, circa early 2000s (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Centre for Documentation and Research. Ministry of Foreign Affairs. UAE: List of foreign publications received by the library, compiled by Afnan El Sukhan. (Abu Dhabi: the Centre), English list, October 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Centre for Documentation and Research. Ministry of Foreign Affairs. UAE. List of foreign publications received by the library, complied by Afnan El Sukhan. (Abu Dhabi: the Centre). Arabic list, October 1979 (Box Oversize 1)
  - Cultural Foundation (The Cultural Foundation, Abu Dhabi), undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cultural Foundation: Jerusalem Festival, (Abu Dhabi: Cultural Foundation), October-November 1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Dalma: itlalah 'ala al-madi = [Delma: a look at the past], by B. Salem al-Qubeisi (Abu Dhabi Printing), 2017 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttahịdah: dirāsah wa-wathāʼiq hạwla tārīkhihā wa-nashʼatihā wa-ʻalāqātihā al-ʻArabīyah wa-al-dawlīyah wa-injāzātihā fī ʻāmihā al-awwal [United Arab Emirates: studies and documents about its history, founding, and Arab and international relations in its first year] (Markaz al-Wathāʼiq wa-al-Dirāsāt = Center for Documentation and Research), 1972 (Volume 14)
    DS247.T85 M3 1972
  - Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttahịdah: dirāsah tārīkhīyah jughrāfīyah hạdạ̄rīyah lil-taʻrīf bi-imārātihā wa-injāzātihā al-muʻāsịrah (Markaz al-Wathāʼiq wa-al-Dirāsāt, Abu Dhabi), December 1972 (Volume 15)
    DS247.T85 D39 1972
  - Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttahịdah (Ministry of Knowledge and Culture), December 1992 (Volume 16)
  - Dubai Municipality. Achievements of Dubai Municipality, 1985-1994 (Volume 17)
  - Dubai Municipality: Awards Won by Dubai Municipality, 2002 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Dubai Municipality. Best Practices, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Dubai Municipality. Information Handbook. (Dubai: Dubai Municipality, 1995) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Dubai Municipality: "Dubai: kharta siyahiyah" [tourist map], 1994 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Dubai Museum: brochure, undated, circa 1990s (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Emirates Film Competition. Daily Schedule, 6th Session, 2007 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Emirates Foundation: "Together we give back to the community" (booklet describing activities, programs, in English and Arabic), undated, circa 2005 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Emirates Foundation: Emirati Youth in Numbers: The National Survey of Youth Wellbeing and Development, undated (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Event honoring Sheikha Fatima bint Mubarak on International Volunteer Day: press releases, plus booklet titled "First Lady of Charity", December 1998 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Fatema bint Mohamed Bin Zayed Initiative (FBMI). "Weaving enterprise and compassion together for a brighter future" [prospectus about Initiative's program to help women weavers in Afghanistan] English and Arabic, undated, circa 2012 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Fujairah Magazine [Arabic], Year 2, Issue 8, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Indian Ladies Association. Jyoti, 1996-1997. (Abu Dhabi: Indian Ladies Association (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Islam in Sicily (Italy. Ministry of Foreign Affairs, and The Cultural Foundation), 2004 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Izzidien, Yousif. Arabic Manuscripts in the National Library of Sofia, "Cyrille et Methode." (Baghdad: Iraq Academy Press, 1968) (Volume 18)
    Z6621.N373.A7 1968
  - Ma'arid al-Kitab al-'Arabi: Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttahịdah, Abu Dhabi (Diwan al-Emiri, Wizarat al-Ulam), Undated (Volume 19)
  - The National (newspaper): "A Nation's Journey: 4 Decades, 4 Stories." [booklet on the occasion of National Day and 40th anniversary of the UAE], National Day 2011 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ortszeit / Local Time: From the peaceful revolution to German unity (Goethe Institut symposium and photography exhibition, Abu Dhabi), October 4, 2009 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Qasr al Hosn Festival: Programme, "Take Part in History." [Booklet, English and Arabic], 20 February - 1 March 2014 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Qatar National Library Digitization Center (Qatar National Library), December 2016 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Roobacker, Cornelis Cornelisz. Scheeps-Journaal, Gamron-Basra (1645)….(Leiden: Brill, 1907) [photocopy] (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Royal Stables - Abu Dhabi, United Arab Emirates [two booklets], Undated, circa 1998 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sharjah. Department of Culture and Information. "Al-Ayam" [newsletter on theatre], March 16, 2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - "Sinbad's Haven. UAE National Museum for Marine Archaeology and Seafloor Treasures." Project Draft. [Typescript, no attribution], Undated, circa 1999 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sir Bani Yas: Haven of Nature (Environmental Research and Wildlife Agency), undated, circa 2000 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - United Arab Emirates (UAE. Ministry of Information and Culture), 1978 (Volume 20)
    DS247.T82 U53 1978
  - United Arab Emirates (UAE. Ministry of Information and Culture), 1992 (Volume 21)
    DS247.T88 U55 1992
  - United Arab Emirates (UAE. Ministry of Information and Culture), 1995 (Volume 22)
    DS247.T8 U14 1995
  - [United Arab Emirates Yearbook, 1977] = al-Kitāb al-sanawī 1977 (Abu Dhabi: Wizarat al-'Ulam wa al-Thaqafah) (Volume 23)
  - United Arab Emirates: From Trucial States to Federation. An Exhibition Celebrating 25 Years of the United Arab Emirates. (UAE. Ministry of Information and Culture), 1996 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Vereinigte Arabische Emirate. Statistik des Auslandes. Länderbericht. (Federal Republic of Germany, Statistische Bundesamt), 1985 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Die Vereinigten Arabischen Emirate (U.A.E. Ministry of Information and Tourism), 1974 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Women's Handicraft Centre, Abu Dhabi (Ministry of Labour and Social Affairs / Union of Women Association), [folder with loose leaves, containing patterns of dresses], Undated, circa 1970s. (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Education, 1989-2009
  - Abu Dhabi Men's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): folder with various brochures, handouts from "Open Day", 1994 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): Administrative Handbook, July 1992 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): Career Fair, and event on recruitment of Emirati nationals into private sector [program, handwritten notes by Frauke Heard-Bey], November 1997 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): Ceremony programs (graduation, student recognition), 2002-2005 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): Faculty Handbook, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): Gibbons, Michael. Higher Education Relevance in the 21st Century. UNESCO. With note of presentation to Frauke Heard-Bey from head of ADWC, Dr. Graddon Rowlands, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): Miscellaneous, and newsletters, 1993-2002 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): The Pearl [yearbook], (1992/1993) (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): The Pearl [yearbook], (1994/1995) (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): The Pearl [yearbook], 1996/1997 (3 copies) (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): The Pearl [yearbook], 1998/1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): The Pearl [yearbook], 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College (Higher Colleges of Technology): Survey of Third Year Students in the Higher College of Technology, "Attitudes of Nationals to the Private Sector", December 1997 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College: The Arabian, Issue 1, Oct. 1996 (Box Oversize 1)
  - Abu Dhabi Women's College: The Arabian, Issue 2, Dec. 1996 (Box Oversize 1)
  - Al Shohub School for Girls (Abu Dhabi): Curriculum information and homework handbook, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Al Shohub School for Girls (Abu Dhabi): GCSE Options, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Al Shohub School for Girls (Abu Dhabi): Prospectus, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Al Shohub School for Girls (Abu Dhabi): Sample forms, undated, circa 2000 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - American University of Sharjah. Folder with prospectus on university and its academic divisions, and notepad with notes taken by Frauke Heard-Bey at lecture., 2004-2005 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Higher Colleges of Technology. Center for Excellence in Applied Research and Training (CERT): handouts, newsletter, 1999 and undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - HCT: Quest: Abu Dhabi Men's College, February 2008 (Box Oversize 2)
  - HCT: Al-Rawi: Higher Colleges of Technology. Monthly Newsletter (Vol. 1:1, Sept. 1993) (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - HCT: Al-Rawi: Higher Colleges of Technology. Monthly Newsletter (Vol. 3:9, Nov. 1995) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - HCT: Al-Rawi: Higher Colleges of Technology. Monthly Newsletter (Vol. 7:7, April 2000) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - HCT: Al-Rawi: Magazine of HCT (Vol. 1, issue 1), Summer 2003. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - HCT: Al Rawi: The Magazine of the Higher Colleges of Technology: Tribute to Sheikh Zayed, Winter 2004 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - HCT: Al Rawi: The Magazine of the Higher Colleges of Technology: Health Sciences, Spring 2005 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - HCT: Al-Rawi. Special issue for Education Without Borders conference, 2011 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Textbook: Lughatunā al-'arabiyah: kitābu wa al-qirā'ah, lil- ṣaff al-awwal al-ibtidā'ī [ Our Arabic Language: writing and reading, for Grade 1, Primary], (UAE. Ministry of Education), 1990-1991 (Volume 24)
  - Textbook: Lughatunā al-'arabiyah: kitābu wa al-qirā'ah, lil- ṣaff al-thānī al-ibtidā'ī [ Our Arabic Language: writing and reading, for Grade 2, Primary], (UAE. Ministry of Education), 1990-1991 (Volume 25)
  - Textbook: Lughatunā al-'arabiyah: kitābu wa al-qirā'ah, lil- ṣaff al-thālith al-ibtidā'ī [ Our Arabic Language: writing and reading, for Grade 1, Primary], (UAE. Ministry of Education), 1990-1991 (Volume 26)
  - Textbook: Social Studies 1, The Local Environment (UAE. Ministry of Education), 1989 (Volume 27)
  - Textbook: Social Studies 2, The United Arab Emirates (UAE. Ministry of Education), 1989 (Volume 28)
  - Textbook: Social Studies 3: The Arabian Gulf And The Arab World (UAE. Ministry of Education), 1989 (Volume 29)
  - Textbook: Dirāsāt al-ijtamaʻīyah: Dawlat al-Imārāt al'Arabiyah al-Mutaḥidah, lil-ṣaff al-khāmis al-ibtidā'ī [Social Studies, 2: United Arab Emirates, for Grade 5, Primary], 1985-1986 (Volume 30)
  - Textbook: Dirāsāt al-ijtamaʻīyah: al-Khalīj wa al-Jazīrat al-'Arabiyah, lil-ṣaff al-sādis al-ibtidā'ī = The Gulf and the Arabian Peninsula. Grade 6 (Ministry of Education), 1985-1986 (Volume 31)
  - UAE University. General Catalog, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - UAE University. Khaleej Times special report, "10 Enlightening Years.", 24 March 1988 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - UAE University: Kitāb al-sanawī lil-kharījīn. Jāmiʻat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttaḥidah. [Alumni Yearbook], 1988-1989 (Volume 32)
  - UAE University. Untitled typescript text, 28 pages, Arabic, about university, undated, circa 1990s (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - UAE University. Voices in English, Issue No. 3, Spring 2002 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Zayed University: Achievers: Official Alumnae Magazine of Zayed University. Vol. 2, Issue 1., Fall, 2003 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Zayed University: Achievers, The Official Alumnae Magazine of Zayed University, Vol. 3, Issue 1: The U.A.E's Greatest Achiever: Baba Zayed, 1918-2004 (2004) (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Zayed University: Graduation. [hardbound book], 2004 (Volume 33)
    LG368.D82 .A372 2004
  - Zayed University: Graduation [program]. Abu Dhabi National Theater, 10 May 2005 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Zayed University: Graduate CV Book, 2005 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Zayed University. Destined to Lead: New Horizons, 2009 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Government publications, 1968-2007
  - Abu Dhabi emirate, and other: general, 1968-2001
    - Abu Dhabi Economic and Social Report, 2008. (Department of Planning and Economy. Studies Division. Studies and Planning Sector) (Volume 34)
    - Abu Dhabi Fund for Arab Economic Development = Ṣundūq Abū Ẓaby lil-Inmāʼ al-Iqtiṣādī al-ʻArabī. al-Nashrat al-Iqtiṣādiyah [Economic Bulletin], 1975 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Abu Dhabi Fund for Arab Economic Development: Administration Department, Telephone Index, October 1977 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Abu Dhabi Fund for Arab Economic Development: "First Annual Report", 1974-1975 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Abu Dhabi Fund for Arab Economic Development. Annual Report, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Abu Dhabi Fund for Arab Economic Development. Annual Report, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Abu Dhabi Fund for Arab Economic Development. Annual Report, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Abu Dhabi Fund for Arab Economic Development. Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Abu Dhabi Fund for Arab Economic Development. Financial and Economic Briefs. Summary, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Abu Dhabi Fund for Arab Economic Development. Financial and Economic Briefs, July-August 1978 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Abu Dhabi Fund for Arab Economic Development. Financial & Economic Briefs, November-December 1978 (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Abu Dhabi: Ministry of Petroleum and Industry. Petroleum and Industry in Abu Dhabi. Vol. IV, 1973 (Volume 46)
      BSN
      BSN: 8125188
    - Abu Dhabi: Ministry of Petroleum and Industry: al-Bitrūl wa-al-sịnāʻah fī Abū Zạbī. Vol. [i.e. No.] 4, 1973 (Volume 47)
      HD9576.U52 A28 1973
    - Abu Dhabi: Ministry of Petroleum and Industry: Akhbār al-Bitrūl wa-al-sịnāʻah [year 3, issue 28], June 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Abu Dhabi: Ministry of Petroleum and Industry: Akhbār al-Bitrūl wa-al-sịnāʻah, [year 3, issue 34], December 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - al-Barnāmaj al-taṭwīrī lil-mashrūʻāt al-ḥukūmīyah: muwazzaʻan ḥasab al-dawāʼir wa-al-qiṭāʻāt al-iqtiṣādīyah, 1988-1992 (Emirate of Abu Dhabi, Planning Department, Economic Division), September 1988 (Volume 123)
    - [Book of Statistics] = al-Kitāb al-ihṣạ̄ʼī (Dāʼirat al-biladiyah Abu Dhabi / Municipality of Abu Dhabi), 1987-1991 (Volume 35)
    - Decrees and Laws Reorganising the Government Structure in Abu Dhabi (Abu Dhabi: Ministry of Information and Tourism), [July 1971] (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - First Population Census of Abu Dhabi, March-April 1968 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - al-Ghābāt wa-juhūd taṭwīr ṣahrāʼ al-Imārāt (Abu Dhabi: Baladiyat Abu Zaby) = [Forests, and efforts to develop the Emirate's desert], 1990 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Policy Agenda 2007-2008, The Emirate of Abu Dhabi (Executive Council) (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Public Works Role in Development = Daur al-Ashġāl fī-at-tanmīya (Ministry of Public Works) [bilingual, English and Arabic], December 2, 1973 (Volume 36)
    - Public Works Role in Development (Ministry of Public Works) [English text only], December 2, 1974 (Volume 37)
      TA113.U57 1974
    - Public Works Role in Development = Daur al-Ashġāl fī-at-tanmīya. (Ministry of Public Works. Arabic text only, other than title), [December 1975] (Volume 38)
    - Statistical Abstract, Volume 2 (Planning and Coordination. Ministry of Cabinet Affairs), July 1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Statistical Abstract, Volume 3 and Year Book 1974 (Department of Planning) (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - [Statistical Bulletin] = al-Nashrat al-iḥṣāʼīyah al-sanawīyah, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Statistical Bulletin. First Nine Months of 1975 (Department of Planning), [October 1975] (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Statistical Bulletin. First Six Months of 1976 (Department of Planning), [July 1976] (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Statistical Yearbook 1975 (Statistical Section. Department of Planning) (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Statistical Yearbook 1975. Emirate of Abu Dhabi. Department of Planning (Volume 39)
      HA4566.Z9 A254 1975l
    - Statistical Yearbook 1986. (Statistical Section. Department of Planning) (Volume 40)
      HA4566.Z9 A254 1986
    - Statistical Yearbook 1987. Emirate of Abu Dhabi. Department of Planning (Volume 41)
      HA4566.Z9 A254 1987
    - Statistical Yearbook 1991. Emirate of Abu Dhabi. Department of Planning (Volume 42)
      HA4566.Z9 A254 1991
    - Water Resources Survey, Interim Report by Sir Alexander Gibb and Partners (Dept. of Development and Public Works, Abu Dhabi), April 1969 (Volume 43)
      HD1698.5 .U54 1969
    - Whitehead and Partners (London): proposal for study of government structure of Abu Dhabi, 21 December 1970 (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Whitehead and Partners (London): "Report on the Structure of Government" (Government of Abu Dhabi), summary, May 1971 (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Whitehead and Partners (London): "Report on the Structure of Government" (Government of Abu Dhabi), expanded version, May 1971 (Box Oversize 3)
    - "Electricity and Water." Annual Report 2005. Emirate of Abu Dhabi. Regulation and Supervision Bureau. (Box 11, Folder [placeholder, to locate])
    - Statistical Yearbook 2001. Economic Department, Government of Ras al Khaimah. (Volume 44)
      HA4566 .F85 2001
    - United Arab Emirates. Emirate of Fujairah. Dept. of Statistics and Planning. Statistical Yearbook, 2001 (Volume 45)
  - Abu Dhabi emirate: al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah = Official Gazette, 1972-2006
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 1, 15 April1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 2, 20 April 1972 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 3, 27 April 1972 (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 4, 4 May 1972 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 5, 11 May 1972 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 6, 18 May 1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 7, 25 May 1972 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 8, 1 June 1972 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 9, 8 June 1972 (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 10, 15 June 1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 11, 2 July 1972 (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 12, 27 July 1972 (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 13, 3 August 1972 (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 14, 7 September 1972 (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 15, 21 September 1972 (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 16, 5 October 1972 (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 17, 26 October 1972 (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 18, 30 November 1972 (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 19, 14 December 1972 (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 1, No. 20, 31 December 1972 (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 1, 1 February 1973 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 2, 1 March 1973 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 3, 1 April 1973 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 4, 5 April 1973 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 5, 12 April 1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 6, 19 April 1973 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 7, 26 April 1973 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 8, 3 May 1973 (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 9, 10 May 1973 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 10, 17 May 1973 (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 11, 24 May 1973 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 12, 31 May 1973 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 13, 7 June 1973 (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). Year 2, No. 14, 14 June 1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)